--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:小鱼  字幕调校:云之容止  招募Q号:76846146
拉
Pull
向右转
Right face
向右拉
Right forward pull
向右走
Right forward march
保持计数
Count keep count
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
One two three four One two three four
保持计数
Count keep count
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
One two three four One two three four
保持计数
Count keep count
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
One two three four One two three four
保持计数
Count keep count
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
One two three four One two three four
保持计数
Count keep count
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
One two three four One two three four
马吉欧 你好
Hey Maggie Hello
你好 普威特
Hiya Prew.
你怎么会来这里？
What are you doing over here?
我从薛福特堡被调过来
Transferred over from Fort Shafter.
- 你离开号角兵团了吗？- 是的
- You quit the Bugle Corps? - Yep.
- 为了来这里？- 不是我自己选的
- For here? - I didn't pick it.
你严重搞错了
Oh you made a very bad mistake.
他们可以把这个军团还给卡斯特将军
This outfit they can give back to General Custer.
是吗？
Yeah?
上尉还没进办公室
Captain ain't in yet.
我四处去看看
I'll look around.
你以为你在干什么？
What do you think you're doing'?
- 你叫什么名字？- 普威特 从薛福特堡调来
- What's your name? - Prewitt. Transfer from Fort Shafter.
我听说过你
I heard about you.
我也听说过你 上士
I heard about you too Sergeant.
这里是步兵团
This here's a rifle outfit Prewitt.
你在太阳下山前不该玩乐的
You ain't supposed to enjoy yourself before sundown.
把球杆收起来 跟我来
Put up your cue and come along.
葛兰昨天去过医院
Grand went to the hospital yesterday. Did you put him in the sick book?
- 你的报告写好了吗？- 我还没有时间写 上士
- Did you make out the morning report? - I didn't have time Sergeant.
你是文书官
You're the company clerk Mazzioli.
医官很晚才将病历送来
Those medics didn't bring back the sick book till late yesterday.
- 我马上就会写的 - 多谢 我已经替你写好了
- I'll tend to it right now. - Thanks. I already done it for you.
你是薛福特堡最棒的号手
You're the best bugler they got over at Shafter.
也是全岛最棒的
You're the best bugler they got on this whole island.
那倒是事实
That's true.
我同情你
I feel for you pal.
但站在我的立场 我还是不了解你
But from my position I can't quite reach you.
立正
Ten-hut
- 稍息 - 早安 长官
- At ease. - Morning sir.
有什么特别的事吗？
Morning men. Anything special for me this morning Sergeant Warden?
- 我只有几分钟时间 - 是的 长官 有新兵报到
- I've only a few minutes. - Yes sir. New man here.
是的 进来
Oh yes. Come in.
长官 罗勃普威特大兵
Sir Private Robert E. Lee Prewitt.
向连长报到
Reporting to the company commander as ordered.
稍息 服役纪录呢？
At ease. Where's that service record?
生于肯塔基州 在维州梅尔堡入伍
Born in Kentucky enlisted first at Fort Myer Virginia.
第一号手
"Bugle Corps First Bugler."
我通常会跟新报到的人谈谈
Prewitt I always make it a policy to talk to my new men.
本军团的运作很顺利
Now I have a fine smooth-running outfit.
如果我欣赏某位士兵
If I like a soldier he can get to be a noncommissioned officer
他便能迅速升任无委任状士官
quicker here than anywhere else.
但他得让我看看他够精明
But he has to show me that he's got it on the ball.
你在号角兵团惹了什么麻烦？
What kind of trouble were you in in the Bugle Corps?
- 没有惹麻烦 长官 - 那么你为何请调？
- No trouble sir. - What made you transfer out then?
那是个人因素
It was a personal matter.
- 你有什么想问的吗？上士 - 是的 长官
- Something you wanted to ask Sergeant? - Why yes sir.
普威特 你原是下士
Prewitt you was a corporal in the Bugle Corps.
你却自动降为大兵 调至步兵团
You took a bust to buck private to transfer to an infantry outfit.
为什么？是因为你喜欢步行
Why? Because you like to hike?
还是你受不了吹号角？
Or was it because you couldn't stand to bugle?
完全是个人因素
It was a personal matter.
这由连长决定
That's up to the company commander to decide.
是怎么样？
Well?
我担任了两年的第一号手
I was First Bugler for two years.
但军士长的朋友调了进来
The topkick had a friend who transferred in from another outfit.
第二天他便成了第一号手
The next day he was made First Bugler over me.
我吹号的技巧比他好
I was a better bugler.
你因此而离开？
And you asked out on account of that?
或许是有些不太理智
Maybe it ain't sensible but that's the reason.
他的情感受到伤害 他们现在给我们的人手是这样的
His feelings were hurt. Kids they send us now
我们会恢复你的官阶 或许还让你升官
Well we'll get your stripes back for you maybe an extra one for good measure.
你知道你为何在参谋本部？
Do you know why you were assigned to "G" Company?
不知道 长官
No sir.
我利用了一些关系 我现在是军团的拳击教练
I pulled a few strings. I'm the regimental boxing coach you know.
是的 长官
Yes sir.
两年前我看了你和康纳斯的一场拳击赛
I saw your fight with Connors in the Bowl year before last.
- 你本应该打赢康纳斯的 - 谢谢你 长官
- You should have won it. - Thank you sir.
去年我们在决赛时败北
Our regiment got beaten in the finals last December
但今年我一定要获胜
but I mean to win this year.
我需要中量级的好手
All I've needed was a top middleweight.
很抱歉 长官 我已不打拳了
I'm sorry sir. I quit fighting.
不打拳？为什么？
Quit fighting? When? What for?
一年多前
Well over a year ago.
或许你听说过 迪西威尔斯的事
Maybe you heard about what happened with Dixie Wells?
你是指受伤的那家伙？
You mean that fellow that got hurt?
- 是的 长官 - 我是听说过
- Yes sir. - Yes I heard about that.
我能了解你的感受 那种事难免会发生
It's too bad. I can understand how you feel. But those things happen.
他是我不打的原因 长官
That's why I decided I would quit sir.
你不能因为死了一个人 就说"停战"
You might as well say stop war because one man got killed.
我们的拳击课程 是最能提振士气的
Our fighting program is the best morale builder we have.
军团已经有一位走音的号手
I've got a mighty sour company bugler.
- 你喜欢这工作吗？- 如果要打拳就不喜欢
- How'd you like the job? - Not if it means fighting.
你打算取得独行侠的声誉吗？
Looks to me as if you're trying to acquire a reputation as a lone wolf Prewitt.
军队里不能有个人主义存在
You should know that in the army it's not the individual that counts.
军团不会对你施加压力
Well you'll find that we won't put any pressure on you in my outfit.
你只要不犯错就行了
Just don't make any mistakes in it that's all.
我要进城去 还有事吗？
I've got to go into town. Anything else for me today Sergeant?
军团的预算报告明天就要交了
The company fund report has got to be made out it's due tomorrow.
- 你写吧 没有其他了？- 没有 长官
- You make it out. Is that all? - No sir.
由你全权处理
Well whatever it is you fix it up.
下午如果有事 代签我的名字
If there's anything that has to go in this afternoon sign my name.
- 我不会回来了 - 是的 长官
- I won't be back. - Yes sir.
如果不是我在后面替他打理
He'd strangle in his own spit if he didn't have me around here
他早就完蛋了
to swab his throat out for him.
走吧
Come on.
你已从军五年？五年半？
You been in the army what now Prewitt? Five years? Five and a half?
是的
Yeah.
你不认为是时候 该学聪明些了吗？
Don't you think it's about time you got smart?
你拒绝了炸药荷姆斯
You know what you did just now when you turned down Dynamite Holmes?
等于是自找死路 当拳击手很轻松
You put your head in a noose. Things are softer for a boxer in this outfit.
你最好学学怎么当兵
Otherwise you'd better know how to soldier.
我当得和任何人一样好
I can soldier with any man.
这里快变成夏威夷皇家饭店了
This place is getting' to be like the Royal Hawaiian Hotel.
- 她是谁？
Who is that?
她是荷姆斯上尉夫人
She's Captain Holmes' wife.
你会被逼赛拳
You'll fight Prewitt.
因为荷姆斯上尉 想成为荷姆斯少校
You'll fight because Captain Holmes wants to be Major Holmes.
他认为赢得拳赛就能升官
He's got an idea he'll make it if he gets a winning team.
就算不为他 也为了我
And if you don't do it for him you'll do it for me.
我的工作就是让他高兴
'Cause my job is to keep him happy see?
他愈高兴 就愈不会来烦我 而且我就会把他的军团 管理得更好
The more he's happy the less he bothers me and the better I run this company.
我们清楚我们的立场吧？
So we know where we stand don't we kid?
我知道自己的立场 不依他的人将一事无成
I know where I stand. A man don't go his own way he's nothing.
在拓荒时期或许还可以
Maybe back in the days of the pioneers a man could go his own way
但是现在你必须照章行事
but today you've gotta play ball.
列瓦
Leva
我能不能走进来之后 看到你用双手在工作呢？
Can't I once walk up to the supply room and find you working with both hands?
你们付我的薪水根本不够
I can't do no better on what you people pay me
替这个人准备些用品 寝室在顶楼
Draw this man some supplies. "G" Company squad room's on the top floor.
把你的袋子放好后再回来
Get rid of your bags and come back here.
列瓦会帮你 可以替你省下四五趟路
Leva will help you lug your stuff upstairs. Save you making four or five trips.
- 谢谢 - 我不喜欢浪费体力
- Thanks. - I just hate to see energy wasted.
你会需要你的体力的
Besides you'll be needing yours.
他看来是个好人
Looks like a good man.
我了解他这种人 他是死脑筋
I know his type. He's a hardhead.
大热天她还穿毛衣
Her and them sweaters.
我想她一定冷若冰霜
I'll bet she's colder than an iceberg.
不会的 军士长 她很懂世故的
Not her Top. She knows the score like I been telling you.
- 是吗？- 别在这里听
- Is that right? - Listen not around here.
我在布里斯堡听说
But when I soldiered at Fort Bliss with Holmes
很多关于这女士的事
I heard plenty about this lady plenty.
- 是吗？- 好吧 不用告诉我了
- You did huh? - Okay not me.
我认识她的伴侣 所以你不用告诉我了
But I know some of the guys she played around with so don't tell me.
我没有 是你在告诉我
I ain't telling you. You're telling me.
- 早安 上士 - 早安 夫人
- Good morning Sergeant. - Morning ma'am.
我来找我丈夫
I'm looking for my husband.
他到城里公干去了
Captain Holmes just went into town ma'am on business.
他说有东西留给我 你知道吗？
He was to have left some things for me. Do you know anything about them?
不知道 夫人 我能效劳吗？
No I don't ma'am. Anything I can do for you?
不用了 谢谢
No thanks.
我很乐意效劳的 夫人
I'd be glad to help ma'am.
我丈夫告诉我很多你的事 上士
My husband's been telling me a lot about you Sergeant.
- 他说你做事的效率很高 - 是的 夫人
- He says you're very efficient. - Yes ma'am.
你为何如此有效率？上士
What is it that makes you so efficient Sergeant?
因为我天生聪颖 夫人
I was born smart ma'am.
我喜欢这个说法 再见了 上士
I love that. Well goodbye Sergeant.
她可真是啊 对吧？
Man she sure is one ain't she?
- 真是什么？- 真是尤物
- One what? - One woman.
我看过更美的
I've seen better.
凯伦？凯伦？
Karen? Karen?
对不起 我回来晚了 - 没有关系
- Sorry I'm late. - It doesn't matter.
我在军官乐部
I got tied up with General Slater.
- 被史莱特将军缠住了 - 恩？
- I bumped into him in the Officer's Club. - Yeah?
- 将军说了些什么？- 他说要成功
- What did the General have to say? - Success he said.
战时要成功 和平时更要成功
Success in war success in peace time.
对我的升官却一句也没提
And not a word about my promotion.
有时我觉得他想降我职
Sometimes I think the old man's just waiting to ship me down.
少去奉承将军们
Well if you'd spend less time buttering generals
多跟你的军团在一起
and more time with your company you'd get that promotion.
军团可以照顾自己
The company takes care of itself.
我今天去找过你
I went over there today looking for you.
我到卡纳欧黑办事
I had some business to attend to at Kaneohe.
你不介意吧？
That was all right wasn't it?
当然 我没有权利过问
Of course. I have no right to inquire into your actions.
- 那是我们同意的 - 为什么要提起这件事？
- That was our agreement. - Then why bring it up?
我可不是你 认为的那种笨女人
Because I wanted you to know I'm not as stupid as you maintain all women are.
这话什么意思？
Now just what does that mean?
- 你又在指控什么了？- 没事
- What are you accusing me of now? - Of nothing.
你跟多少女人出去 也不干我的事 对吧？
It's no longer any of my business how many women you go outwith is it?
但我希望你能诚实
But I wish you could just be honest about it once.
为什么要隐瞒？
There's no reason I should try to hide anything is there?
我们之间已经这样了
The way things are between us now
你凭什么一直这样指控我？
what right have you to always be accusing me?
凭什么？
What right?
你还要再翻旧帐吗？
Are you going back to that again?
我还得忍受多久？
How long will it be I wonder before I'm allowed to live that down?
我得跟你说几次那是意外？
How many times do I have to tell you it was an accident?
拜托你 唐纳 我要睡了
Please Dana. I'm going to bed.
请离开我的卧房
Please get out of my bedroom.
荷姆斯上尉说你不想打拳
Captain Holmes says you don't want to come out and fight for us.
没错
That's right.
我请你暍杯啤酒而且谈一谈
We thought we'd buy you a beer and talk it over.
我们是军团的拳击手
We're the company boxers.
我猜也是
I figured.
我真希望他在
Man what I would not give to have this character
我家乡的弹子房
in the corner pool room in my hometown.
如果你跟以前一样打得好 我们就赢定了
Box as good as you used to we'd be a cinch this year.
别忘了 区冠军还可以 放十天的假
You ain't forget division champs get 10-day furloughs did you son?
我是艾克葛罗维奇 是你的排长
I'm Ike Galovitch platoon guide of your platoon.
别以为你很强悍 普威特
And don't think you're a tough guy Prewitt.
现在不说话 到野外可就要喊救命了
You no talk now but out in the field with us you sing different song.
如果他不想打拳 就用不打
Listen the guy don't have to fight if he don't want to without getting' kicked around.
我们正在打撞球 走开
Now we're playing pool. Why don't you take off?
- 你讨打吗？马吉欧 - 不
- You want busted head Maggio? - No.
你最好少管闲事
Then keep your big nose out altogether.
下礼拜开始集训…
Training season starts next week. You can pick up your stuff...
我已告诉过荷姆斯
Look I told Holmes and I'm telling you.
现在我告诉你 我不打拳了
I ain't fighting. I quit fighting.
我已经不打拳了 你们可以尽管威胁我
You guys want to put the screws on go right ahead
- 你想做什么 我能忍受 - 好了 普威特
- I can take anything you can dish out. - Okay Prewitt.
谢谢
Thanks.
我不喜欢看到好人被欺负
I just hate to see a good guy get it in the gut.
习惯吧 小子 你在死之前 会常见到的
You better get used to it kid. You'll probably see a lot of it before you die.
你真够胆 对吧？
You don't scare easy do you Prewitt?
军队有规定我一定要打拳吗？
Do you know anything in army regulations says I gotta box?
本军团的每个拳手都是 无委任状士官
Every boxer in this outfit's a noncom.
你不曾见过他们 聚集在一起给某人特别训练
I guess you've never seen a bunch of them get together and give a man the treatment.
你怎么会称她小妞？她已经四十五岁了
What do you mean "chick"? She's 45.
对你来说还太年轻
She's still too young for you.
我比你好多了 别忘了
Now listen Warden I'm a better man than you any day and don't forget it.
我不会忘的
I won't forget it.
华登是怎么回事？
What's the deal with him anyway?
我不了解他
With Warden. I don't figure him.
华登
Warden?
他不像别人
He ain't like the others.
他会对你很严厉
He'll make it tough on you.
但他会划定一条公平界线 而且会谨守份际
But he'll draw himself a line he thinks fair and he won't come over it.
现在很少有这种军士长了
You don't see many topkicks like him no more.
他在十五军团时 在上海作战
He was with the 15th in Shanghai when they saw their action.
连在菲律宾的我 也听说过他的战绩
I heard about it down in the Philippines even.
我只知道 他是我见过最好的军人
All I know is he's the best soldier I ever saw.
(密语 战术调整) 2 3 4
Hut Hut Hut two three four
(密语 战术调整)
Hut Hut
答数 继续答数
Count keep count
1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4
One two three four One two three four
跟上脚步 普威特
Prewitt Get in step Prewitt
(密语 战术调整)
Hut Hut
这是出操 可不是野餐 快跟上脚步
Prewitt this is a drill not a picnic. Get in step
(密语 战术调整)
Hut Hut Hut
立定
Platoon halt
持枪立正
Order arms
向左转
Left face
普威特 向前一步 走
Prewitt one step forward march.
你的步法好像暍醉的鸟一样
Prewitt you march like a drunken gooney bird.
我来教你出操 留在原地
I gotta teach you how to drill. You stay here.
小队解散
Platoon dismissed
士兵 向右转
Detail right face
小步前进
Trail forward march
半面向左转
Half left march
半面向右转
Half right march
右翼进军
Right flank march
左翼进军
Left flank march
向后转 1 2 3
To the rear march One two three
向后转 后转 后转
To the rear march Rear march Rear march
后转 后转 后转 后转
Rear march Rear march Rear march Rear march
组合武器 预备 开始
Assemble your weapons. All right start.
来福枪是你最好的朋友
A rifle's your best friend.
如果在战斗中卡住了 可能会让你丧命
In case it jams in combat it could mean life or death.
你一定得学会蒙着眼 也可以组合与拆解
So you gotta learn to strip them down and put them back together again blindfolded.
你的后瞄准器不准
Your rear sight's way off.
你在瞄准三百码时会误失五十尺
You'd be 50 feet off target at 300 yards.
士兵不了解他的武器 就会发生这种状况
Now that's what happens when a soldier don't know how to assemble his rifle.
跑七圈 把枪举在胸前
Seven laps around the track double time and keep this rifle at high port.
保持向前
Forward thrust hold
向前 恢复
Draw and recover hold
手臂保持向前
Arm thrust hold
向前 恢复
Draw and recover hold
休息
And rest
懂了吗？普威特
Wide open huh Prewitt?
或许再七圈你就懂了
Maybe seven more laps will teach you to watch yourself.
你疯了？我看到你做的事了
Are you crazy? I saw what you did
她是个大麻烦
I'm telling you Top she's nothing but trouble.
别再想你在想的了
You better keep your mind off what you're thinking.
你想在李汶渥斯监狱终老吗？
What do you wanna do wind up in Leavenworth?
我赶不上归营号了
I won't be back in time to take retreat Sergeant.
- 或起床号 - 是的 长官
- Or reveille either. - Yes sir.
只管工作没有娱乐 上士
All work and no play Sergeant.
你只会做文书工作
All you do is sit around sweating over papers.
除了工作还有其他事情
There are other things in the world besides work.
- 多多出去走走 华登 - 我一直在考虑这件事
- You ought to get out more yourself Warden. - I've been considering it.
我要走了 事情就留给你处理 上士
Well I'm going. I'm leaving it in your care Sergeant.
你回来时全部都会做好 长官
It'll be here when you get back sir.
原来是华登上士
Well if it isn't Sergeant Warden.
快进来 你会被雨淋湿
You'd better step inside or you'll get wet.
我已经湿透了
I am wet.
如果你想找上尉 他不在家
If you're looking for the captain he isn't here.
假设我找的不是他呢？
And if I'm not looking for him?
他还是不在
He still isn't here.
我是要找他 你知道他在哪里吗？
Well I'm looking for him. Do you know where he is?
我不晓得
I haven't the slightest idea.
或许他又"到城里公干"
Perhaps he's "in town on business."
前几天你是这么说的 对吧？
That's the way you put it the other day isn't it?
我有些重要文件得请他签名
I got some papers it's important for him to sign.
我打电话到俱乐部试试
I'll try phoning him at the club. Maybe he's there.
别那么做
Don't do that.
我不想打扰他的酒兴
I never like to disturb a man when he's drinking.
我自己也想暍一杯
I could use a drink myself.
你要邀我进去吗？
Aren't you gonna ask me in?
酒就在那边柜子里 上士
The liquor's there Sergeant in the cabinet.
你冒了极大的危险 我的女佣随时可能会到家
You're taking an awful chance you know. My maid is liable to be home any time.
星期四是她的公休日
No she won't. Thursday's her day off.
你一切都想好了 是吗？
You think of everything don't you Sergeant?
我试着 这个职务必须如此
I try. In my position you have to.
这真的很重要吗？
Are these really important?
是的 但明天也可以
Yes. But not important to get signed today. Tomorrow's okay.
我还有副本 很容易就能处理
I got copies at the office so it won't be much work to fix them up.
我喜欢 上士 你很有自信
That's what I like about you Sergeant. You have confidence.
这也是我不喜欢你的地方
It's also what I dislike about you.
这不是自信而是诚实
It's not confidence ma'am. It's honesty.
我不愿意见到美人独守空闺 浪费了
I just hate to see a beautiful woman going all to waste.
你是说浪费吗？
"Waste " did you say?
我可以告诉你很多跟这有关的事
There's a subject I might tell you something about.
我知道好几种浪费 上士
I know several kinds of waste Sergeant.
你可能不知道其中一些
You're probably not even remotely aware of some of them.
你有兴趣听听吗？
Would you like to hear?
比如家里没有孩子？
For instance what about the house without a child?
也可以算是一种
There's one sort for you.
还有另外一种
Then there's another.
你干得好 上士
You're doing fine Sergeant.
我丈夫在休假
My husband's off somewhere
外头下着雨 而我们两个都在喝酒
and it's raining outside and we're both drinking now.
或许你只误判了一件事 那就是夫人我
You've probably only got one thing wrong the lady herself.
或许我并不像外表那样
The lady's not what she seems.
如果你明白我的意思 她过气了
She's a washout if you know what I mean.
我相信你明白我的意思
And I'm sure you know what I mean.
你想哭吗？
You gonna cry?
我一定忍住不哭
Not if I can help it.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我要走了 那不是你所希望的吗？
I'm leaving. Isn't that what you want?
我不知道 上士 我不知道
I don't know Sergeant. I don't know.
加把劲男孩
Step on it boy
- 快一点 - 我是很快
- Speed it up. - I'm speeding.
够了 马吉欧 你想领钱吗？别闹了
All right Maggio. You wanna get paid? Knock it off.
安杰罗 1美元 他不该出现的
Angelo a dollar he's wrong coming up.
嘿 老兄 过来
Hey paisan come here
对不起 我已经赢了不少钱
Sorry gentlemen I already won my bankroll in the latrine.
而且你们赌注太少
Besides it's a penny-ante game.
好了 你这里藏得什么？
All right what are you covering here?
快点 小子 我们要进城去
Come on buddy boy we're goon' to town.
别让他们惹恼你
Look don't let them get your goat.
我们可以穿便服 看起来跟别人一样帅
We'll just dress up in civvies and we're as good as the rest of the world ain't we?
来 穿这件
Here wear this.
是我姐姐寄来的 她买的东西都太大了些
My sister sent it to me. She buys everything too big.
我们先去几家酒吧逛逛
Look first we'll hit a few bars see?
我是新国会俱乐部的会员
Then we go to a place of which I'm a member the New Congress Club.
女孩们
Girls.
你对女人有偏见吗？
You got any prejudices against girls?
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
你已经为今晚准备整齐了
Well now looks like you're all primed for a big night Top.
- 你好 斯塔尔克 - 你想找个伴吗？
- Hello Stark. - Want some company?
不用了 谢谢 我都约好了
No thanks. All tied up.
列瓦说你在觊觎上尉的老婆
Leva tells me you've been eyeing the captain's wife
就像猎狗在狩猎时一样
like a hound dog at hunting time.
他这么说吗？他还告诉你什么？
He has huh? What else did that character tell you?
她在布里斯堡跟过很多男人
She took up with a lot of men back there at Fort Bliss.
我对那些故事没信心
Well I wouldn't put stock in stories like that.
这可不是故事 因为我也是其中之一
This ain't no story 'cause I was one of them myself.
只是为期不长 她真的有点奇怪
Not for long though. Sure is something strange about that woman.
谢谢你的提醒
Yeah. Thanks for the tip.
回头见
See ya.
你好
Hello.
- 我没想到你会来 - 为什么不？我并没有迟到
- I didn't think you were coming. - Why not? I ain't late.
没有 但是我早到了
No I guess you're not. But then I got here a little early.
我一定是太过焦虑了 但是你没有
I must have been overanxious. You weren't though were you?
我先去暍了几杯
I stopped along the way for a couple of drinks.
好美的地点
You certainly chose a lovely spot for our meeting.
五分钟内就有三个人来约我
I've had three chances to be picked up in the last five minutes.
对这样来说是差不多
Well that's par for the course around here.
我不在意 我从不曾有过秘密恋情
Well I don't care for it. I never went in much for back-alley loving.
放轻松
Take it easy.
你一定认为我是水性杨花
You probably think I'm a tramp.
你为什么认为我会那样想？
Now what makes you think I'd think a thing like that?
用不着这么客气 上士
Don't try to be gallant Sergeant.
如果这是个错误 直说无妨
If you think this is a mistake come right out and say so.
我想我该回家了 不是吗？
Well I guess it's about time for me to be getting home isn't it?
- 不是吗？- 怎么了？
- Well isn't it? - What's the matter?
是什么让这一切开始的？
What started all this anyway?
如果这是个错误 我还会来吗？
Do you think I'd be here if I thought it was a mistake?
冒了在李汶渥斯待二十年之险
Taking a chance on 20 years in Leavenworth
只为了陪伴连长夫人？
for making dates with the company commander's wife?
而她的态度像亚斯特夫人的马 只因为我准时到达
And her acting like Lady Astor's horse And all because I got here on time
我在衣服里穿了游泳衣
Well on the other hand I've got a bathing suit under my dress.
我也一样
Me too.
她来了
She's coming.
这不是安杰罗马吉欧吗？
Why it's Angelo Maggio
你好 奇佛太太
Greetings Mrs. Kipfer.
你来了 甜小子 钱都付清了
There you are sweetie pie. Dues all paid up.
是谁在弹琴？河马吗？
Hey who you got playing the piano there? A hippo?
我没见过你的朋友
Oh Angelo I don't think I've met your friend.
罗勃普威特大兵
Private Robert E. Lee Prewitt.
我讨厌你这个样子
Oh you know how I hate it when you boys are in this condition.
你看到过那个男孩？
You see that buddy boy?
女人看见一位士兵 而且她认为他暍醉了
A woman sees a soldier and like that she figures he's drunk.
- 为什么？你知道为什么吗？- 因为他是暍醉的
- Why? You know why? - Because he is.
暍酒不能跟娱乐业混为一谈
Well heavy drinking simply doesn't mix with the entertainment business.
我们得考虑我们的未来
Every respectable place has to consider its future.
跟我们一起 你的未来很安全
Mrs. Kipfer ma'am you have my solemn word your future will be safe with us
安杰罗是我最爱的客人之一
Angelo is one of my favorites.
阿妮特 请替我招呼这位客人
Annette dear take care of this gentleman for me will you please?
一共四块钱 娃娃脸
That'll be four bucks baby face.
两块钱入会费 两块钱月费
Two for initiation fee two for this month's dues.
我能得到什么？
What do I get for it?
俱乐部所有特殊待遇
Members are entitled to all privileges of the club
跳舞 饮料吧
which includes dancing snack bar soft drink bar
还有与异性风雅的消遗
and gentlemanly relaxation with the opposite gender
不可以暍酒
so long as they are gentlemen and no liquor is permitted.
- 明白了吗？- 明白了
- Got it? - I got it.
女孩们 又来了新毒药 这是比利珍和南西
Girls here's some new poison. This is Billie Jean and Nancy.
- 很高兴认识你 - 你好
- Nice meeting you. - Hi there.
别告诉我 你喜欢公主那种型
Don't tell me the princess is your style.
这两位是苏珊和萝珊
This is Suzanne and Roxanne.
- 你好 - 你想跳舞吗？甜心
- Hello there. - Would you like to dance honey?
嘿
Hey
很感谢你的陪伴 但可否容我失陪？
Much as I adore your company I hope I may be allowed to tear myself away.
我看到门口有朋友
I just saw a few friends at the door
看来你已经用不着我了
and I can also see that I will be of no further use to you.
嗨 你忙吗？
Hi. You busy?
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
我叫萝琳
I'm Lorene.
萝琳是吗？
Lorene huh?
我以前不曾见过你
I haven't seen you in here before.
我没有来过这里 是我朋友带我来的
I haven't been in here before. My friend brought me.
我们驻扎在雪菲德
He and I we're stationed out at Schofield.
我没想到你是军人
Oh I didn't think you were a soldier.
- 这是什么意思？- 好吧 我…
- What do you mean? - Well I...
我今年三十岁 我可是全心奉献
I'm a 30-year man. I'm in for the whole ride.
当男人把它当成事业时 就完全不一样
Well I suppose it's different when a fella's gonna make a career of it.
当兵并没有什么不对
Ain't nothing the matter with a soldier that ain't the matter with everyone else.
我还是一样喜欢你
I like you just the same.
- 我一看到你就喜欢你 - 是吗？
I liked you the minute I saw Annette bringing you in.
真好玩 当我进来时 看到你坐在这里
You did? It's funny I came in I stood there and saw you sitting over here.
停下来或者用个消音器
Why don't you knock it off or put a mute in that thing
我想弹多大声都行 义大利佬
I'll play loud as I want you little wop
义大利佬？
Little wop?
我要修理你 胖子
Mess with me fat stuff and I'll bust you up.
你急着找大麻烦 义大利佬
You must be in a hurry for trouble wop.
- 在这里等我 - 没问题
- Wait right here for me will you? - Yeah sure.
你知道的我不会…
Gentlemen you know I will not...
墨索里尼在教我弹琴
This little Mussolini here is trying to tell me how...
你弄伤了我的耳膜
Like to bust my eardrums with the stinking noise
- 拜托 - 别打了
- Let's not be cruel. - Break it up Angelo.
如果你不能守规矩就得离开
You men will just have to go if you can't behave yourselves.
- 只有朋友能叫我"义大利佬" - 知道他是谁吗？
- Only my friends call me wop. - Do you know who that guy is?
- 我不在乎 - 他是谁？
- What do I care who he is? - Who is he?
胖子贾德森 禁闭室的警卫士官长
Fatso Judson Sergeant of the Guard in the stockade.
我叫你别搭理他
I'm telling you let him alone.
我看过他差点杀了人 他乐在其中
I seen him nearly murder a guy once. He likes it.
好吧 你赢了战争 我们跳舞 恩？
Okay bully boy now you won the war. Let's dance huh?
好的 我们跳舞 我们跳舞 我得先镇静一下
Yeah we'll dance we'll dance. First I gotta calm my nerves.
我们到电话亭去
Let's go to a phone booth or something huh?
我要把藏在夏威夷衫下的 一大瓶威士忌暍掉
Where I will unveil a fifth of whiskey I have here under my loose-flowing sports shirt.
别受伤了 朋友
Don't get hurt pal.
你一定要有无讹的平衡感
Your balance has got to be letter perfect.
我以为你在等
I thought you were gonna wait.
- 比尔正在说冲浪的事 - 你好 朋友
- Bill here was telling me about surfboarding. - Hello friend.
坐下来听 他讲得很刺激
Just sit down and listen. He describes it thrillingly.
你知道冲浪吗？
Do you know anything about surfboarding?
完全不了解
No nothing. Not a thing.
我住在迪罗西所以有很多机会
You must be stationed inland then. I'm at DeRussy so I get lots of chances.
但是我们有山
Yeah but then we got mountains.
你知道如何爬山吗？
Do you know anything about mountain climbing?
一点点
A little bit.
- 你很会爬山吗？- 不会
- You a mountain climber? - No.
你会开飞机吗？
Do you know anything about flying an airplane?
我上过几堂课
I've had a few lessons.
我也不会开飞机 你对于深海潜水了解多少吗？
I can't fly either. What do you know about deep-sea diving?
我们去别的房间
Bill shall we move into another room?
好的 空气好像变得很混浊不是吗？
Sure. The air in here seems to have gotten lousy hasn't it?
- 我也注意到了 - 听着 老兄…
- I noticed that. - Listen fella...
走吧 我们走
Come on let's go.
深海潜水夫怎么了？
How was the deep-sea diver?
你的态度糟透了
That was a terrible way you acted.
或许我只是嫉妒
Maybe I was jealous.
你真的很好玩
You're a funny one.
你们女人到底想怎样？玩弄男人到死吗？
What do you dames want? To tease a man to death?
奇佛太太付钱请我们 对所有男人好
What do you think Mrs. Kipfer hires us for? She pays us to be nice to all the boys.
他们都一样 这很重要吗？
You're all alike. Is it so important?
是很重要 或许我们很相像但我们并不一样
It is important. We may seem all alike. We ain't all alike.
对不起
I'm sorry.
听着…
Look...
我们到奇佛太太的接待室坐一下
Let's go up to Mrs. Kipfer's parlor and sit there.
她让我们用来接待特别贵宾
She lets us use it sometimes for somebody special.
我去问她
I'll go ask her.
- 你不生气了？- 不气了
- Then you're not mad? - No I'm not mad.
如果你生气了 我宁可不再继续
Because if you're still mad I'd just rather we called the whole thing off.
你真的是个好玩的家伙
You certainly are a funny one.
我从来不知道是这样子的
I never knew it could be like this.
没有人像你这样吻过我
Nobody ever kissed me the way you do.
没有人？
Nobody?
没有
No nobody.
一个都没有？你所吻过的所有男人？
Not even one? Out of all the men you've been kissed by?
那可得好好算算
Now that'd take some figuring.
- 你想有多少人？- 我不知道
- How many men do you think there've been? - I wouldn't know.
- 告诉我一个估计 - 没有计算机算不出来
- Can't you give me a rough estimate? - Not without an adding machine.
- 你有计算机吗？- 我忘了带
- Do you have your adding machine with you? - I forgot to bring it.
那么我想你是不会知道
Then I guess you won't find out will you?
或许我已经知道了
Maybe I already know.
怎么了？你在暗示什么？
What's the matter? What are you hinting at?
有什么好暗示的吗？
Why? ls there something to hint at?
搞不好有过很多海滩派对
Maybe there's been a long line of beach parties.
- 你一定是疯了 - 是吗？
- You must be crazy. - Am I?
你跟荷姆斯 在布里斯堡又如何？
What about when you and Holmes were back at Fort Bliss?
你听说过史塔克大兵吗？梅隆史塔克？
Did you ever hear of a soldier named Stark? Maylon Stark?
是 知道的
Why yes.
"是知道的"你也认识他 对吧？
"Why yes." You knew him too didn't you?
对吧？
Didn't you?
你跟其他人都一样
I had to go and forget you were like all the rest of them.
那些事都是真的 对吧？对不对？
Only it's true ain't it? Well ain't it?
你为什么不告诉我？
Why don't you tell me about it? Tell me the story.
总是有故事的
There's always a story.
你不留给任何人任何余地 对吧？
You don't leave a person anything do you?
回来 上士 我会把故事告诉你
Come back here Sergeant. I'll tell you the story.
你可以把故事带回营区
You can take it back to the barracks with you.
我只结婚了两年 就发现他有外遇
I'd only been married to Dana two years when I found out he was cheating.
当时我已经怀孕 让我有了可以期待的事
And by that time I was pregnant. I thought I had something to hope for.
阵痛开始那晚 我差点觉得高兴
I was almost happy the night the pains began.
唐纳去出席军官会议
I remember Dana was going to an officer's conference.
我告诉他要早点带医生回来
I told him to get home early to bring the doctor with him.
那会议不是和女人开的话 他就会照办
And maybe he would have if his conference hadn't been with a hat check girl.
他到了凌晨五点才暍醉了回来
He was drunk when he came in at 5:00 a.m.
当时我躺在地板上
I was lying on the floor.
我求他去找医生 可是他醉倒在沙发上
I begged him to go for the doctor but he fell on the couch and passed out.
孩子在一小时后生了下来
The baby was born about an hour later.
当然是死了 是一个男孩
Of course it was dead. It was a boy.
他们送我到医院急救
But they worked over me at the hospital. They fixed me up fine.
他们救活了我 还免费替我割了盲肠
They even took my appendix out. They threw that in free.
- 凯伦？- 还有一件事 我也不能生育了
- Karen? - And one more thing. No more children.
我是跟男人出游 看看我能否找到一个…
Sure I went out with men after that and if I'd ever found one that...
凯伦 听我说
Karen listen to me. Listen.
我知道
I know.
直到我遇见你 我也认为这是不可能的
Until I met you I didn't think it was possible either.
我也到军中服务 独自一人离开奥勒冈的家
I enlisted too. I came out here on my own to get away from my hometown in Oregon.
怎么会？
How come?
我原本是个女侍
I had a boyfriend.
我男友来自最富裕的家庭
I was a waitress and he was from the richest family in town.
他娶了一个符合地位的女孩
He just married a girl suitable for his position.
当时他已与我交往了三年
After three years of going around with me.
很棒的故事吧？这个故事可以写一本书
It's a pretty story isn't it? Maybe they could write a book about it.
写过了 太多人写了
They did. Thousands of them.
所以我离家到了西雅图
So I left and went to Seattle.
我遇见一个从夏威夷回去的女孩
I got there and I met a girl just back from Hawaii
她在那里赚了大钱
and she said she'd made a lot of money working there.
所以我搭上第一班船
So I caught the first boat.
我已经来这里一年两个月
I've been here a year and two months.
而你并不喜欢不是吗？
You don't like it very much do you?
我是不喜欢但我并不在意 我不会永远待在这里
Oh I don't like it but I don't mind it. Anyway I won't be here forever.
当然不会 为什么要呢？
No. Sure. I mean why should you?
再过一年我就会赚了很多钱 回家去了
I got it all figured out. In another year I'll be home with a stocking full of money.
之后我可以重新过生活
And I'll be all set for life.
哪一位？
Who is it?
我没有听到争吵声 所以以为你们也想暍一杯
I didn't hear no sounds of combat so I thought you might want a drink.
你独占那瓶威士忌 安杰罗
- You've been hogging the whiskey Angelo. - Not me buddy.
不是我 是珊卓拉 她是很好可是太会暍酒了
It's that Sandra. She's a nice girl but she drinks like a fish.
我希望下面有警察
I hope there's a cop under that.
继续倒
Keep pouring. Keep pouring.
不了 谢谢 我不暍酒 我觉得那是个缺点
No thanks. I don't drink. I think it's a weakness.
我允许你的看法
I grant you that.
我不喜欢缺点 你呢？
I don't like weakness. Do you?
不喜欢 但我想喝酒
No I don't like weakness but I like to drink.
你要嫁给这家伙吗？
Hey what are you gonna do marry this guy?
你对他笑的样子好像是他老婆
You're grinning at him like you're his wife.
滚出去
Get out of here.
好…
Okay okay. I'm goon.
我要回去找长腿珊卓拉
Back to old long-legged Sandra. I love them tall.
我喜欢腿长 绵延不绝
Acres and acres.
好好享受 老兄 你比我更需要这个
Enjoy yourself paisan. You need this more than I do.
明天你得继续接受特训
Tomorrow you'll be back with the treatment.
他是什么意思？
What does he mean?
你在他面前依偎在我身边真好
Hey that was nice before the way you snuggled up in front of him.
什么是特训？
What's a "treatment"?
有些人因为我不打拳 所以对我施压
Oh some of the guys putting me over the jumps 'cause I don't want to fight.
打拳？
Fight?
是的 参加拳击队 我不想打拳击
Yeah on a boxing team. I don't want to box. I don't even want to think about it.
你为什么一定要打拳呢？
Well why should you have to box?
我以前是打中量级的
Well see I used to fight.
而且我打得很好
Middleweight. And I was pretty good.
他们大家都知道
They know it. Well anyway...
快点告诉我 我想听
Well come on tell me. I want to hear.
当时我跟一个叫
Well the thing is see...
迪西威尔斯的人练习
I used to work out with this guy Dixie Wells.
他是我的一位好朋友
He was a real good friend of mine.
他很喜欢拳击 外头的人都看好他
Loved to box. People on the outside had their eye on him.
他原本可以晋到最高级
He was gonna come out of the army and go right up to the top.
有天下午 我跟他在健身房练习对打
Well one afternoon he and I were sparring around in the gym
你知道 就是友善那种打法
you know kind of friendly-like
他可能是太累了
and he must have been set pretty flat on his feet
因为我不过是…
because I caught him with a...
用普通力气打了他一记右拳
No more than ordinary right cross...
他没有爬起来 动也不动
And he didn't get up he didn't move.
他昏迷了一个礼拜 最后终于清醒了
He was in a coma for a week and finally he did pull out of it.
可是他却瞎了
Only the thing was that he was blind.
我到医院去看了他几次
Well I went to see him at the hospital a couple of times
后来我再也无法去看他
then finally I just couldn't go back.
最后一次当我们谈起拳击
The last time he and I started talking about fighting and...
他开始哭
He started to cry.
看着那双瞎了
And seeing tears coming out of those eyes
的眼睛流着泪
that couldn't see anything.
我应该告诉你 荷姆斯跟他的拳手谈过了
I thought I oughta tell you. Holmes spoke to his boxers last night.
从现在开始 不会对你客气
From now on it's no holds barred.
他们打算将你逼进禁闭室
They aim to run you right into the stockade if they got to.
任由他们
Let them.
我会帮你 可是我不能太过明显
I'll help you as much as I can but I can't get too far out on a limb.
我不会牺牲自己的军阶 我喜欢这个军团
I ain't risking losing my stripes. I like this outfit.
我也一样 真好笑 不是吗？
So do I. That's funny ain't it?
是的 是很好笑
Yeah. Yeah that is funny.
保持一直线 普威特
Keep going' in a straight line Prewitt.
继续走
Keep going
好了 够了
All right that's enough.
普威特 把它埋了
Okay Prewitt bury it.
我顺利的星期一
My hitch was up Monday
不是个失败的士兵
Not a dog soldier no more
我不再是个士兵
I ain't a soldier no more
他们给了我所有的钱
They gave me all that money
多到我口袋很沉重
So much my pockets is sore
喔 我口袋很沉重
Oh my pockets is sore
耶 是个男生
Yeah that a boy
钱多到用不完
More dough than I can use
从军去
Reenlistment blues
唱
Sing it boys
时间到
Time
把这里清干净 普威特
Clean up the mess Prewitt
快 这是劳动 可不是在度假
Hurry it up You're on fatigue detail not a vacation
- 快点 把它清干净 - 你自己清
- Come on Clean it up - Clean it up yourself
什么？
What?
要清你自己去清理
You heard me. Rub your own nose in it a while.
你不该跟无委任状士官顶嘴
Prewitt you know better than to talk back to a noncommissioned officer?
是的
Yes sir.
但我可不喜欢 被无委任士官侮辱
But I've never liked being spit on sir not even by a noncommissioned officer.
你应该向他道歉
You owe Sergeant Galovitch an apology.
绝不 长官 是他该向我道歉
I don't think so sir. I think Sergeant Galovitch owes me an apology.
- 帕路索下士 - 是的 长官
- Corporal Peluso? - Yes sir?
让这个人全副武装
Have this man roll a full field pack extra shoes and helmet
带他去跑可洛可洛山路  然后再带他来见我
take a bicycle and hike him up to Kolekole Pass and back then bring him to me.
- 是的 长官 - 好了 普威特 我们走
- Yes sir. - All right Prewitt let's go.
时间
Time
等一下
Hold it a minute.
抽根烟吧 我跟你一样不喜欢这种事
Go ahead Prewitt and have a cigarette. I don't like this any more than you do.
谢谢
Thanks.
你预备好向 葛罗维奇士官道歉？
I take it you're ready to apologize to Sergeant Galovitch now?
不 长官 我不道歉
No sir I'm not.
帕路索 再带他去跑一圈
Peluso take him up there again.
是的 长官 好了 普威特 我们走
Yes sir. All right Prewitt let's go.
你不能善待这种人 他好像是头野兽似的
You can't be decent to a man like that. You have to treat him like an animal.
上士 准备军法审判的表格
Sergeant prepare court-martial papers.
罪名是抗命
Insubordination to a noncommissioned officer.
是的 长官
Yes sir.
- 只是太可惜了 - 怎么了？
- Only it's a shame. - What is?
你将会失去一名中量级好手
Well I was just thinking sir It's too bad you've gotta lose a good middleweight.
我不需要忍受他的无礼
I don't care. I don't have to stand for that kind of insolence.
不 长官 当然用不着
No sir you sure don't.
我马上准备表格
I'll prepare the papers then.
就算他只被判刑三个月
The only trouble is that even if he gets just three months
决赛时他会待在禁闭室中
he'll still be in the stockade when the boxing finals come up.
你有办法说服他吗？
Do you see any other way of breaking him?
你可以加重惩罚 长官
Well you could double up on company punishment sir.
我会用重刑
All right. I'll throw the book at him.
如果你那么觉得的话 长官
Yes sir if you think that's the way to do it.
好建议 上士
Nice going Sarge.
继续看的话 你会发现自己在刷地板
Keep looking Mazzioli you'll find yourself scrubbing this orderly room floor
借过 我和服务生们已经忙坏了
Coming through Watch it Me and my waiters are working our tails off.
烫 烫
Hot Hot H-So-T
你好吗？在这里比被关禁闭好
How you doing buddy boy? Better than being thrown in the stockade ain't it?
我好吗？我是个粗人
How am I doing Sarge? I'm a rough man man.
慢一点 汗别滴到菜上
Slow up a little there Angelo so you can stop sweating in the food.
不要阻止我 中士 不要阻止我
Don't hold me back Sarge. Don't hold me back.
我正在申请升下士 你成功不了的
I'm putting in for corporal tomorrow. Well you'll never make it.
- 你好 中士 - 你好 军士长
- Hiya Sarge. - Hiya Top.
一生都得待在步兵团里
Life in a rifle company.
你看起来很累的样子 小子
You look awful tired kid.
你喜欢连续当班吗？
How do you like straight duty?
- 你认为我会介意吗？- 我没有那么说
- What makes you think I mind it Warden? - I didn't say you minded it.
我只是说你看来很累的样子 好像快崩溃似的
I just said you looked tired. You know drawn to a fine edge.
我喜欢这种生活 棒极了
Oh I like this life. It's a great life.
如果我找到珍珠 我会算你一份
If I find a pearl I'll cut you in.
跟你平分 知道吗？
Fifty-fifty. You know what I mean?
如果不是你让我来这里 我不会有机会去找它
If you didn't put me here I'd have no chance to find it right?
现在你有机会了 你知道什么？
Now there's a man for you. What do you know?
既然你喜欢 我会再多替你找一些
Since you like it so much I'll see if I can find some more for you.
垃圾小队怎么样？
How about garbage detail?
谢了 礼拜三已经做过了
Thanks. I had that on Wednesday.
原来做过了 那么扫街如何？
So you did. What about street cleaning?
- 昨天扫过了 - 你的记忆力比我的更好
- Yesterday. - You got a better memory than me.
当然 如果你聪明的话…
Of course if you were smart...
说得是 但我并不聪明
Yeah but I ain't smart.
但如果你聪明 你就用不着做炊事兵
I know but if you were you wouldn't have to pull K.P.
或者其他劳动工作
or any other fatigue duty for that matter.
如果你认为可以说服我打拳 那你就错了
If you think you can bribe me into boxing Warden you're wrong.
你错了 你没有办法 荷姆斯跟特训也办不到
You're wrong. Not you and Dynamite Holmes and the treatment.
你还要压迫普威特多久？
How long are you guys gonna keep breaking it off on that kid Prewitt?
你已连续一个月罚他加班了
You've had him on that extra duty roster a month already.
- 我不明白为什么你… - 皮特你不行吗？
- I can't see why you... - Can't you Pete?
年纪大心也变软了吗？
What's the matter you getting soft in your old age?
或许我是在给他些教训
Maybe I want to teach the kid a lesson.
- 或许是你喜欢这样 - 或许我是喜欢
- Maybe you like it. - Maybe I do.
我不想再看你做荷姆斯的爪牙
I'm getting sick and tired watching you being a stooge for Holmes.
你不会再看多久了
Yeah well you ain't gonna see it much longer.
我自己也很厌烦
I'm getting sick and tired of it myself. I'm through Pete.
我随时都可以不干 真的
Any day now and I mean it
只要荷姆斯允许 我宁可明天就请调
Listen if Holmes would let me I'd transfer out of here tomorrow.
有半打以上的军团会争取我
There's half a dozen companies in this regiment that'd grab me.
- 而且还会有官阶 - 当然
- And in grade too. - Oh sure.
我还可以做参谋长 但我不能离开我的弟兄
I could be chief of staff too only I just can't think of leaving my old buddies.
你要上哪儿去？应声虫
Where are you going Little Sir Echo?
去冲澡 除非士官长反对
To take my shower if the stinking First Sergeant has no objections.
你以为了呢？去看电影吗？
Where'd you think? To the movies in this towel?
快点 我们去暍几杯啤酒
Hurry up. We'll get some beer.
就算那是世上最后的啤酒也不去
I wouldn't drink with you if it was the last beer in the world.
我请客
I'm buying.
那就不一样了
That's different.
哇
Wow
萝丝
Rose.
知道为何我喜欢你为我服务？
You know why I like to have you serve me beer?
这样我才能看着你走开
So's I can watch you when you walk away.
你有权抱怨
It's in regulations. You got a right to complain.
你可以去向督察长申诉
You got a right to take your case to the inspector general.
任何士兵都可以 就连普通二等兵都行
Any soldier has even a plain dogface.
不 我不会去申诉
No. I ain't gonna complain.
我不会让他们得到满足的
They ain't gonna get that satisfaction.
不管你信不信我有一大家人
Believe it or not this is one soldier that's got a real big family.
一共十五人 这里只有一半而已
Fifteen of them 'course this is only half of them.
你看到那个留八字胡的先生？
You see the gentleman with the handlebars? That's Mr. Maggio.
那是我父亲 马吉欧先生
Mr. Maggio is my father.
从没见过如此顽固的人
Never saw anybody so stubborn.
离他们上次让你进城有多久了？
How long is it since they let you go into town?
- 六个星期 - 搞不好会六年
- Six weeks. - It's liable to be six years.
六年你都看不到女人
How'd you like it six years before you see a dame?
你何不管好自己的事？
Look why don't you just mind your own business huh?
你为什么不去学吹号角？
And where did you learn to play the bugle?
那才是我的好兄弟
That's my buddy boy
这小妞是谁？
Who's the broad?
是我姐姐
My sister.
马吉奥你在干嘛？
Maggio what are you doing'?
- 你打我 - 没错 而且我会再打
- You hit me - Yeah and I'm about to do it again too.
- 你这个肮脏的义大利佬 - 想打就到外面解决
- Why you dirty Wop - If you want to fight take it outside
我要切下这义佬的心脏
I'm gonna cut this wop's heart out.
如果有人敢插手 我会先修理他
Anybody steps in here I give it to him first.
再往前一步 胖子 我就会砍了你的脑袋
One step further Fatso and I'm gonna de-brain you. I'll kill...
这里只有我才可以杀人
Nobody's gonna do nothing Anybody does any killing around here I'll do it
- 这是私事 - 不
- This is a private affair Warden. - No it ain't
他属于我的军团
This man's in my company
不要无缘无故的替我制造麻烦
You ain't making two extra weeks' paperwork for me for nothing.
非打不可吗？
Out for blood huh?
搞不好会把胆汁都吐出来
You'd puke your guts out at the sight of a dead man.
把凳子放下 把它放下
Put down that stool. Put it down
把刀子扔掉
Drop that knife.
好吧 胖子 如果你想杀人就来吧
Okay Fatso if it's killing you want come on.
来吧
Well come on.
丢到地板上
On the floor
杀手？我宁可用你们 来交换一个女童军
Killers huh? I'd trade the pair of you for a good Camp Fire girl.
泼猴
Tough monkey.
你这种人迟早会被关禁闭
Guys like you end up in the stockade sooner or later.
总有一天我会等着你被关进来
Someday you'll walk in I'll be waiting.
到时我会要你好看
I'll show you a couple of things.
我要出去呼吸点空气
I'm gonna get a breath of air.
我很高兴他阻止了这件事
I'm glad he stopped it.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
你留着
You keep it.
留做纪念
Keep it for a souvenir.
好吧 我会留着
Okay I'll keep it.
你不太有机会享受生活吧？小子
You ain't enjoying life much are you kid?
普鲁伊特
Prewitt.
你周末想放假吗？
Could you stand a weekend pass?
可以吗？
Could I...
荷姆斯怎么办？
What about Holmes?
别担心 我放在他面前的文件 他都会签字
Don't worry about Holmes. He signs anything I put in front of him without reading it.
我会用的到的
Sure could use it.
听说你迷恋上 新国会俱乐部一位小姐
I hear you gone dippy over some dame down at the New Congress Club.
- 她叫什么名字？- 萝琳
- What'd you say her name was? - Lorene.
好美的名字
Beautiful name.
嗨 老兄
Hey paisan
是什么绊住你了？我们走
What's holding you up? Let's get going?
怎么了？你不喜欢这里吗？
What's the matter buddy boy? Don't you like it here?
你难道有更好的去处？
You got something better to do in town?
巴士就快开了 我要赶去搭车
Look the bus is leaving right away. I'm taking the bus right?
快走 我是有钱人 我会搭计程车
Take off. You're talking to a rich man. I'll hop a taxi.
我到卡拉库瓦跟你碰面
I'll meet you at the Kalakaua later.
马吉欧 预备上哨
Maggio get ready for guard.
戴宽边毡帐 子弹腰带 武器
Campaign hat cartridge belt and weapon.
十分钟内报到
Report to the orderly room in 10 minutes.
什么？我有假单
What? I got a pass
那不算 安德生病了 所以你得上哨
Not anymore. Anderson's sick. You're on guard.
我昨天上过哨 为什么是我？
I just had guard yesterday. Why me?
我告诉你原因 你换衣服速度应该快一点
I'll tell you why you. You should've gotten dressed faster.
你在回避我吗？
I sure never figured in your giving me the runaround.
- 他们甚至不让我进来 - 我们被围攻那就是为什么
- They didn't even want to let me in this place. - We're mobbed that's why.
这里有一大群希坎军营来的人
There's a big crowd from Hickam Field and they got in here first.
你到底想怎么样？
Anyway what'd you expect a brass band to meet you?
- 我以为你会想见我 - 我正在忙 看到了吗？
- No. I did think you'd want to see me. - I'm busy can't you see?
- 是的 我看到了 - 我是在忙
- Yes I can see. It's crowded. - Well I am.
马吉欧待会儿会去卡拉库瓦
Look Maggio's gonna be at the Kalakaua Inn later.
难道你不能想办法离开吗？
Ain't there no way you can get out of here?
你到底怎么搞的？
What's the matter with you?
我在这里工作 你不懂吗？
I work here you know after all. Can't you understand?
是的 我当然明白 我非常明白
Yes I do. I understand I understand very well.
你几个礼拜都没有来 现在突然出现…
You haven't been around here in weeks and now you turn up all of a sudden and...
小心 老兄 走路要看路
Watch it Mack Watch where you're going
我们到外面去
Come on out of here.
奇佛太太有规定 我不能这样就走掉了
Don't you think Mrs. Kipfer has rules? I can't just walk out.
我们不能在外面跟男孩约会
And even if I could she doesn't like us to see the boys on the outside.
如果你是这种感觉那就算了
Look if you feel that way just forget about it okay?
你管不着我
You haven't any claims on me Mister.
- 你又不是我丈夫 - 原来你在这里 萝琳
- You're not my husband you know. - There you are Lorene.
我欣赏你的品味但我们需要她
I vastly admire your taste my dear but we really need Lorene now.
有许多位先生没有人陪伴 真是忙坏了
So many of the gentlemen are unattended. It is such a rush isn't it?
- 是啊 - 搞不好有人会误解
- Yeah. - One might almost mistake us...
我们在开大型政治会议
For one of those big political conventions in Philadelphia.
- 你来吧？萝琳 - 马上来
- You are coming Lorene? - In a minute.
- 对不起 - 你认为我有什么感觉？
- I'm sorry. - How do you think I feel?
搞不好我几个月都无法拿到假条
I may not get another pass for months.
我期待这次见面 就像小孩期待耶诞节一样
I've been counting on this like a kid counts on Christmas.
还是算了吧 萝琳在忙 萝琳很抱歉
But forget it. Forget it. Lorene's busy. Lorene has got work to do. Lorene's sorry.
别再叫我萝琳 我的本名叫艾玛
Oh stop calling me Lorene My name's Alma
- 艾玛？- 是的 艾玛伯克
- Alma? - Yes Alma Burke
艾玛？
Alma?
奇佛太太从香水广告上 挑了萝琳这个名字
Mrs. Kipfer picked "Lorene" out of a perfume ad.
她觉得这个名字很有法国风味
She thought it sounded French.
你怎么脱身的？
Hey how'd you get away?
我说我病了
I told Mrs. Kipfer I was sick.
- 但我打赌她并不相信 - 我赌她不信
- But I bet she doesn't believe it. - I bet she doesn't.
- 你想暍什么？- 可乐 谢谢
- What'll you have? - A coke please.
给她可乐 大可乐
Yeah give her a Coke. Big Coke.
你能来这里见我真好
It's great you meeting me here you know?
我是运气好才能进城
See I'm just lucky getting in town.
- 军士长饶了我 - 他们还在施压吗？
- Topkick gave me a break. - They still pouring it on?
他们真的让我快要崩溃
Holmes and those others they really got me on the edge.
- 你一定很恨军队 - 不 我不恨它
- Gee you must hate the army. - No I don't hate the army.
但把你折磨成这样
But look what it's doing to you.
我爱军队
I love the army.
但它一定不爱你
But it sure doesn't love you.
男人爱一样东西 并不表示一定有所回报
A man loves a thing that don't mean it's gotta love him back.
没错 但人的忍耐有限
Yeah but a person can stand just so much.
你爱某件事 你应该感恩
You love a thing you've got to be grateful.
我在十七岁时离家
See I left home when I was 17.
我的父母亲都死了 我没有归属感直到入伍为止
Both my folks is dead and I didn't belong no place till I entered the army.
而且我还学会吹号角
If it weren't for the army I wouldn't have learned how to bugle.
- 吹号角？- 是的
- To bugle? - Yeah.
这个吹口就是我在 阿灵顿公墓吹丧葬号时用的
That's the mouthpiece that I used when I played a Taps at Arlington.
他们选我在休战纪念日 吹奏丧葬号角
They picked me to play a Taps at Arlington cemetery on Armistice Day.
总统也到场
The president was there.
我的号角吹得很好
I play the bugle well.
嗨 老百姓
Hello citizens
- 你上哪儿去了？- 你好 帕尔斯
- Hey where you been? - Hi pals.
我已经去过三家酒吧 我对三家酒吧都做了些奉献
I've been in three bars and I put a dent in all three of them.
- 没错 看来就像 - 给我些酒 我很想要
- Yeah you look it. - Give me a nail Prew. I'm hungry for a nail.
你怎么会穿制服？
What you doing in uniform?
我正考虑从军
I'm thinking of joining the army.
或许我该到墨西哥当牛仔
Or maybe I'll go to Mexico and become a cowboy.
你愿意跟我一起去吗？
You want to go with me?
你再继续喝酒就会像溶掉的蜡烛一样游泳
You keep on drinking you'll be as much use as a melted candle.
你说得很对 酒保 威士忌
You're absolutely right. Bartender whiskey
大杯的
Large whiskey.
借过 老兄
Excuse me. Hey buddy.
山姆
Sam
各位 金贝地下室的怪物 就要出笼了
Hey coming out fellas. The terror of Gimbel's basement.
让开 出个七点 五点 两点
Stand back there now. Here we go. A seven for daddy. Five deuce.
七点
Hey seven.
两个么点 那正是我一生的高潮
Snake eyes. That's the story of my life.
夏威夷皇家饭店就在附近
Hey Prew that's the Royal Hawaiian Hotel around the corner.
电影明星常在那里出现
That's where all those movie stars stay.
你最好安静下来 你还有整个周末要过
Listen paisan you'd better simmer down. You got a whole weekend ahead of you.
那是你说的 兄弟
- That's what you say buddy. - What do you mean?
- 他们只给你过夜假条吗？- 没有假条
- They only gave you an overnight pass? - No pass.
他们让我上哨 可是老安杰罗骗过他们了
No pass at all. They put me on guard duty but old Angelo he foxed them.
你擅离岗哨？
You walked off guard?
我签到之后立刻签出
I checked in and I checked right out again.
你赶快回到岗哨去 你的麻烦大了
You get your tail right back to the post. You're in trouble. You know that.
我有个好主意
Hey hey Prew Prew I got a good idea.
我们去跟电影明星游泳
Let's go swimming We'll go swimming with a movie star.
我正打算那么做 去跟电影明星游泳
That's what I'm gonna do go swim with a movie star
听着安吉洛…
Listen Angelo...
二十尺高 我要去跟电影明星游泳
Twenty feet tall I'm going swimming with a movie star.
你最好快走吧
You'd better go.
嘿 安吉洛
Hey Angelo.
混球 快走来 醒醒
Jerk get up. Wake up.
我是清醒的 你干嘛大吼？
I'm awake I'm awake. What are you hollering?
把衣服穿上
Yeah you're awake. Put your clothes on all right?
把它们送给印第安人 他们会需要的
Give them back to the Indians. The Indians need the clothes.
他们只穿丁字裤
All they wear is G-strings.
你没有暍醉 快起来
You ain't drunk. Come on get up.
我要在这里等电影明星 从饭店里出来
Hey I am waiting here for a movie star to come out of the hotel
除非她出现否则我不会走
and I am not going until she shows up.
把衣服穿上
Put your clothes on.
在我们惹上麻烦之前赶快离开
Let's get out of here before we get in trouble okay?
你是怎么回事？难道我不能暍醉吗？
What's the matter with you? Can't a man get drunk?
难道我不能做自己想做的事？
Can't a man do nothing?
难道我不能手插在口袋里 走在大街上吗？
Can't he put his lousy hands in his lousy pockets on a lousy street?
难道我必须一生被追逐吗？
A man gotta be hounded all his life?
我累了 我又不是罪犯
Well I'm tired. I ain't no criminal.
- 我也不是懦夫 - 兄弟 你瞧
- I ain't no coward - Buddy boy look.
你把衣服穿好 快把衣服穿上
You get dressed you put your clothes on.
- 等我 我去叫计程车 - 是才怪
- Will you wait for me? I'll get a cab. - Yeah yeah sure.
- 你会等吧？- 是的 你去叫计程车
- Will you wait? - Yeah you get a cab.
嗨 宪兵你们快来抓我
Hey M.P.s Come and get me you guys
我在这里
Here I am
你们只能这样吗？我想你们一定是吃脆麦片的
Is that the best you can do? I bet you guys eat Wheaties
军事法庭有消息吗？
Any word on Maggio's court-martial yet?
- 现在正在审 - 他一定会被关禁闭
- It's on right now. - He'll get the stockade sure.
或许他不会被关
Maybe he won't get it.
他只不过是暍醉了
All he did was to get drunk.
那是军人的本色 偶尔变成义务了
It's a soldier's nature. It's almost his sacred duty once in a while.
可是他擅离职守
But he walked off guard. He went A.W.O.L.
- 你为什么在这里？- 男子汉不能休息吗？
- What're you hanging around here for? - Can't a man rest?
什么男子汉？你没事做吗？我可以派一些给你
What man? You got no work? Maybe I can scare you up some.
去打几杆撞球 有任何消息我会通知你
Go on and shoot some pool. Any word comes through I'll let you know.
参谋本部 华登上士 是的 长官
Company First Sergeant Warden speaking. Yes sir.
我会把他的东西准备好
Yes sir I'll have his things in order.
他被判刑了 六个月
He got it. Six months.
金贝的地下室关不了我
I'm gonna escape from this dump.
禁闭室也一样关不住
Gimbel's basement couldn't hold me neither can no lousy stockade.
- 闭嘴 - 全听你的 女童军
- Shut up. - Whatever you say Brownie.
囚犯 停
Prisoner halt
你好 泼猴
Hello tough monkey.
我们很幸运能租到它
This other girl and I were lucky to rent it.
这是个迎合潮流的好区
This is a very fashionable district.
我替你打了钥匙
I have another key made for you.
你随时都可以用它 就算我不在也可以
You can use it any time you want to even when I'm not here.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
普威特就是我跟你提起的大兵
This is Prew the soldier I told you about.
- 乔琪特 我的室友 - 欢迎你 朋友
- This is Georgette my roommate. - Well welcome friend.
自从那只猫死了以后 屋里就没有男的了
There hasn't been a man around the house since the cat died.
我每次必订阅书会的书
I belong to the Book Guild Club. I always take every book.
那是我分得红利的方式
That's the way I get all the dividends.
等马吉欧出禁闭室后 她会很适合他
She'll be great for your friend Maggio when he gets out of the stockade.
是的 他会为她疯狂
Yes he'll be crazy about her.
请坐 让自己舒服一下
Just sit down and get comfortable.
我去替你调杯马丁尼 再去准备晚饭
I'll make you a martini and see what's to cook for dinner.
感觉好像结了婚 对吧？
Hey this is like being married ain't it?
好比结了婚
It's better.
你还好吗？
You Okay?
很高兴你来了吗？
Glad you came?
我们走吧 不要回头
Let's get out of here. Don't look around.
我们不能再这样继续下去
It can't go on like this much longer.
就算是到了岛这一头 我们还是得…
Even when we sneaked clear across the island tonight
像囚犯一样逃跑
we had to run out like jailbirds.
如果我们有办法…
If there was only some way we...
荷姆斯会让你离婚
Holmes would probably give you a divorce
可是他不会让我请调
but he'd never let me transfer out of his outfit.
是有一个办法
There is a way.
我一直在考虑这件事 你必须去做军官
I've been thinking about it. You've got to become an officer.
就读新的额外课程
You can take the new extension course the one they passed last May.
然后他们就会送你回美国
When you get your commission they'd ship you back to the States.
当军官？
An officer?
是的 这样我可以跟 唐纳离婚再嫁给你
Yes. Then I could divorce Dana and marry you.
我讨厌军官 我一直很讨厌军官
I hate officers I've always hated officers
那可是个很明智的看法
Well that's a fine intelligent point of view.
如果我说我讨厌上士呢？这样合理多了
Suppose I said I always hated sergeants? That'd make a lot of sense wouldn't it?
你已经研究得很透澈
You sure made a complete study of it.
好吧 假设我是研究过 别以为这事很容易
Okay suppose I did it. And don't think it's a cinch.
我在美国时你就可以离婚了
Then you'd be getting your divorce here while I was in the States.
我们必须分开六个月 到时我们一定会参战
We'd be apart maybe six months. We're sure to be into a war by then.
老实说吧
Why don't you tell the truth?
你只是不想负责任
You just don't want the responsibility.
搞不好你根本不爱我
You're probably not even in love with me.
你疯了 真希望我不爱你
You're crazy I wish I didn't love you
或许我可以再次享受人生
Maybe I could enjoy life again.
于是他们结了婚 从此过着不快乐的生活
So they were married and lived unhappily ever after.
在我遇见你之前 我从不曾如此悲惨
I've never been so miserable in my life as I have since I met you.
我也没有
Neither have I.
我不愿再抛弃一分钟
I wouldn't trade a minute of it.
我也不愿意
Neither would I.
或许我会成为 你见过最差的军官
I'll probably make the lousiest officer in this man's army you ever saw.
你一定会是个好军官
You'll make a fine officer.
一个很棒的军官
A remarkable officer.
谢谢你
Thank you.
过来
Come here.
难道你不能等我们吃完晚餐？
Can't you wait until we finish dinner?
- 亲爱的 - 什么事？
- Honey? - What?
我想娶你
I want to marry you.
你真是个好玩的家伙
You're a funny one.
为什么有人想娶你 是件好玩的事？
Why? Why is it funny if a guy wants to marry you?
因为你是在 新国会俱乐部认识我
Because I'm a girl you met at the New Congress Club.
那只不过比最底层高一点而已
That's about two steps up from the pavement.
我是什么？不过是个大兵 没有阶级的大兵
Well what am I? I'm a private no-class dogface.
大部分的人会认为我什么都不是
The way most civilians look at that that's two steps up from nothing.
我以为我们很快乐
Prew I thought we were happy.
你为何要毁了这一切？
Why do you want to spoil things?
听着 我还有一年就要延役
Look I've got a year to go before I reenlist.
如果到时候我能升为士官 我就可以回美国
If I can swing sergeant's stripes by then they'll let me go back to the States.
到时我们可以一起回去 如果你愿意等的话
Then you and I can go back there together if you'll wait.
你在荷姆斯手下如何升成士官？
How do you expect to become a sergeant under that Captain Holmes of yours?
你只能尽量不被关禁闭
It's all you can do to keep out of the stockade.
我愿意打拳击
I'll fight.
- 不 你用不着打拳击 - 那是值得的
- No you're not gonna fight. - It'd be worth it.
现在我们彼此是相爱
Prew it's true we love each other now
我们相互需要
we need each other
但回到美国 就可能大不相同
but back in the States it might be different.
那不是真正的理由
That ain't the real reason.
- 好吧 那不是 - 什么是真正理由？
- All right it's not. - What is the real reason?
我不想成为士兵的太太
I won't marry you because I don't want to be the wife of a soldier.
我最好只能为你做到那样
Well that would be about the best I could ever do for you.
因为没有人能妨碍我的计划 没有任何人或任何事
Because nobody's gonna stop me from my plan. Nobody. Nothing.
因为我想做高尚人
Because I want to be proper.
- 高尚？- 是的 高尚
- Proper? - Yes proper.
再过一年 我的钱就存够了
In another year I'll have enough money saved
我打算回到奥勒冈
and then I'm gonna go back to my hometown in Oregon
替我妈和自己盖楝房子
and I'm gonna build a house for my mother and myself
然后加入乡村俱乐部 学打高尔夫球
and join the country club and take up golf.
我会遇到有高尚地位的高尚男士
And I'll meet the proper man with the proper position
我将成为高尚的太太 掌高尚的家 生养高尚的孩子
and make a proper wife who can run a proper home and raise proper children.
我会很快乐 因为高尚的人很安全
And I'll be happy because when you're proper you're safe.
你很有勇气 亲爱的
You got guts honey.
我希望你能成功
I hope you can pull it off.
当我说需要你时是真心的
I do mean it when I say I need you
因为我很寂寞
because I'm lonely.
你认为我在说谎 对吧？
You think I'm lying don't you?
没有人会用寂寞来说谎话
Nobody ever lies about being lonely.
不要跟我提离婚的事
And don't talk to me about a divorce.
为什么？难道丑闻会 破坏你升迁的机会？
Why? Because the scandal would spoil your chances for a promotion?
我要知道对方是谁
I ask you once more.
以及你是在哪里认识他的
I want to know who he is and where you met him.
我绝对不会告诉你
I'm not going to tell you.
我知道他是个老百姓 你谨慎的不会找军人
One thing I know. I know he's a civilian. You'd be too discreet to pick an army man.
我不知道是你的骄傲 还是你的好奇让我重伤？
I wonder which is hurt more your pride or your curiosity?
你不会知道我的感受
You can't expect to know how I feel about a thing like this.
为什么男人的感觉如此不同？
I wonder why men feel so differently about it than women.
根本完全不一样
It's just not the same.
今天天气真好 我想去散个步
It's a lovely day. I think I'll go for a walk.
嘿
Hey.
我听说你才关完禁闭出来
I hear you just got out of the stockade.
那里真的很难捱 我不想再多说
It was rugged. I kept my mouth shut and I didn't get in no trouble.
你有见到马吉欧吗？
Did you see Maggio?
胖子把马吉欧折磨得很惨
Fatso's really got it in for Maggio.
他甚至用了警棍
He's using a billy too.
专打看不到的地方 比如说背后或胸前
Places where it won't show in the back in the chest.
他甚至有个系统
He's got it down to a system.
他还经常踢他
He kicks him a lot too.
你知道马吉欧的反应如何？
You know how Maggio's taking it?
他一直对胖子吐口水
He just keeps spitting in Fatso's eye.
他真有个性 是吗？
Ain't he a hot one?
他是一个好人
He's a good man.
老胖子伤不了他
Well Fatso can't make a dent in him.
那个胖子是个聪明人
But that Fatso he's smart.
值星官从来看不到什么的
He makes sure the O.D. never sees nothing.
为什么马吉欧不向值星官报告？
Why doesn't Maggio go to the O.D. himself?
我们曾鼓励他去报告但他不肯
We tried to get him to but he won't peep.
他真的很倔强
That boy's about the toughest nut in the woods.
你认为他能平安吗？
You think he's gonna be all right huh?
- 他可能快崩溃了 - 这话什么意思？
- Well maybe he's cracking at that. - What do you mean?
胖子将他关进洞裹 就是 单人牢房后…
After Fatso threw him in the hole that's solitary
他开始不停地说他要如何逃跑
he started talking a couple of times about how he's gonna escape.
他说他某个晚上会来找你
He said to tell you he'll look you up one of these nights.
你还趴在地上吗？普威特
Still on your knees huh Prewitt?
拳击决赛在下个月 十二月十五日
Well boxing finals next month. December 15th.
你还有时闲帮我们赢得冠军
You've still got time to help us win the championship.
你是否以加入本军团为荣？
Are you proud to be in this company or not?
我不会再绕过你了
I ain't gonna move around you again.
看来你需要点教训
Something tells me you need a lesson Prewitt.
或许我会亲自教训你
Maybe I'll give it to you myself.
别惹他 他是我小队上的人
Come on leave him alone Ike. He's in my detail now.
如果你打架 麻烦可就大了
You're gonna get in trouble if you fight around here.
- 回去工作 - 别档路
- Get back to work Prew. - Get out of the way
我很乐意提供推荐信
I'll be glad to put my recommendation on that Warden.
你有功绩 经验和官阶
You've got service experience grade.
- 你一定会成为好军官 - 谢谢你 长官
- You'll make an excellent officer. - Thank you sir.
军团里能有你这种人 也是值得让我骄傲的事
It'd be a feather in my cap too. A man from my company.
出了什么事？
At ease. What's the trouble Sergeant?
葛罗维奇和普威特 他们在外头打架 长官
They're fighting outside sir. Galovitch and Prewitt.
普威特？
Prewitt?
葛罗维奇会杀了他 长官
Galovitch looks like he's gonna murder him sir.
我会处理
I'll take care of it.
- 难道你不想看吗？- 不想 你也别看 出去
- Don't you want to see? - No Nor you either Get out of here
为什么普威特不打他的头？
Why don't Prew go for his head?
他曾打瞎某个人所以很害怕
He blinded a guy once. Must be scared of the same thing.
揍他的脸
The face Prew Hit him in the face
拜托 葛罗维奇 公平竞赛
- Come on Galovitch fight fair - I'll fight any way I want
我想怎么打都行
Come on Prew Get him
那位军官应该阻止这场架
Why doesn't that officer stop that fight?
- 他叫什么名字？- 荷姆斯上尉 长官
- What's his name Major? - Captain Holmes sir.
立正
Ten-hut
稍息 是谁先动手的？
At ease. What started this?
普威特违抗我给他的命令 开始顶嘴并且挑衅
Prewitt refused order I gave him talked back and started a fight.
所以我才会教训他
I taught him a lesson.
你不可以再抗命
You won't disobey any more orders in my company Prewitt.
长官 这件事不能怪普威特 是葛罗维奇上士起头的
Sir I'm sorry sir but Private Prewitt's not to blame Sergeant Galovitch started it.
- 索希尔 - 是的 长官
- Thornhill. - Yes sir.
这个小队是你带的 到底怎么回事？
You're in charge of this detail. What about it?
他说得对 普威特没有犯错
He's right sir. Prewitt done nothing.
是葛罗维奇起的头
Yes sir. Galovitch started it.
够了 这事算了 回去做自己的工作
That's all. Let's forget it. Let's get back to our jobs.
好了 回去工作 动作快 解散
All right back to work. Let's go. Break it up.
如果你认为这样我就会出赛 你就错了
If you guys think this means I'm stepping into a ring you're wrong.
你的伤口最好擦点碘酒
You'd better put some iodine on them cuts.
星期二带钱到镇上
Took my dough to town Tuesday
给自己找张大的羽毛床
Found me a big feather bed
喔 大羽毛床 大的双人床
Oh a big feather bed A big double bed
明天我会找到工作
I'll find a job tomorrow
今晚我会睡死
Tonight I'll sleep like I'm dead
I'm gonna sleep like I'm dead
起床后我会选择
And get up when I choose
从军去
Reenlistment blues
星期五
Hey Friday.
-  你怎么会叫星期五？- 我也不知道
- Why are you called Friday? - I don't know.
我是在星期三生的
But I was born on a Wednesday.
星期三我到酒吧
I hit the bars Wednesday
认识一些朋友
Made me some friends on my own
和他们在一起
Lotta friends on my own
找到一个漂亮宝贝
Found a pretty baby
她无法离开我
She couldn't leave me alone
喔 离开我
Oh leave me alone
她让我一直买酒
She kept me buyin' booze
从军去
Reenlistment blues
我星期四很悲惨
I had the misery Thursday
墙壁在移动
The walls was moving' I swear
我发誓它们在移动
Oh they was moving' I swear
我摸到我的裤子
I reached down in my trousers
我的口袋空空
And all my pockets was bare
那女孩不是好事
That gal was sure bad news
从军去
Reenlistment blues
普威特 你要去哪里？
Hey Prewitt where you going?
什么意思？我要去裘伊酒吧 再多买罐啤酒
What do you mean where am I going? I'm going to Choy's.
我要再喝一杯
I'm gonna get me another beer.
我顺利的星期一
My hitch was up Monday
不是个失败的士兵
Not a dog soldier no more
不再是个失士兵
I ain't a soldier no more
别动
Halt
- 谁在那里？－ 一个朋友
- Who goes there? - A friend.
朋友 请你上前表明身分
Advance friend and be recognized
立正
Ten-hut
向后转 向后转走
Right face Rear face
跪下 刷地板
On your knees Scrub the floor
稍息
At ease.
小子 你一个人在这做什么？
Hello kid. What are you doing out here all by yourself?
- 我去买酒 - 坐下 我还有一瓶
- I'm gonna get a little drink. - Sit down. I got a bottle.
谢谢 军士长
Thanks Top.
我一定得称赞你 揍葛罗维奇的方法 小子
I gotta hand it to you kid the way you beat up old Galovitch this afternoon.
可惜他们迟早会扳倒你
Too bad they gotta get you sooner or later.
生命就是这么烂 你知道吗？
Life's crummy you know it?
是的 长官 是很悲惨 非常的悲惨
Yes sir it's miserable. Perfectly miserable.
如果现在有车两卡车
What do you suppose would happen
开过来撞上我们怎么办？
if a truck was to come along and run us over?
- 我们就死定了 - 你最好别再坐在这里
- We'd be dead. - You'd better not sit here anymore.
起来坐到路旁去
You'd better get up and sit over on the side of the road.
你在说什么？我… 可是…
What? What do you mean I better?
你比我更需要活下去 你还得照顾整个军团
You've got more to live for than I do. You got your whole company to take care of.
你快移到路旁
You move over move over to the other side of the road.
我年纪比较大 死了没关系
- Go on. - I'm older It don't matter if I die.
但你有你的一生 现在别争了
But you got your whole life ahead of you. Now don't argue.
- 快点起来- 不 长官 普威特不去
- Go on get up. - No sir not Prewitt.
普威特决定待到苦果的最后
Prewitt stays right here to the bitter end.
好吧 我们一起留在这里
Okay we'll stay together.
反正我也站不起来
I don't... I couldn't have got up anyway.
我惹了世界上最大的麻烦
I got the biggest troubles in the whole world.
世界级的吗？
In the whole world huh?
都是因为爱
Take love.
你曾经见过爱情吗？
Did you personally ever see any of this love?
你不明白我的意思
You'll understand what I mean.
这个女孩
This girl see
她要求我成为…
she wants me to become...
- 成为什么？－一名军官
- Become what? - An officer.
你能想像我当军官的样子吗？
Can you see me as an officer?
可以 我能想像你当军官
Yeah. Yeah I can see you as an officer.
- 你一定会是个好军官 - 你们两个比我有远见
- You'd be a good officer. - Well you both can see more than I can see.
我不想当军官 我很喜欢现在这样
I don't wanna be an officer. I'm happy where I am.
搞不好我会变成荷姆斯那种人
I might turn out to be a guy like Holmes.
你不希望我跟荷姆斯一样吧？
You wouldn't want me to be a guy like Holmes would you?
你会吗？
Well would you?
男人应该做自己在行的事
A man should be what he can do.
你的女朋友呢？
How's your girl?
再告诉我一次她的芳名
What's her name again?
- 萝琳 - 对了 就是萝琳
- Lorene. - Oh yeah Lorene.
我现在想起来了
I remember now.
好美的名字
A beautiful name.
美极了
Beautiful.
你们两个愚蠢的疯家伙
You two dumb crazy screwballs
你们想找死吗？
What are you trying to do get yourself killed?
你们在这里做什么？
What are you doing in the middle of the road?
我的朋友普威特跟我 坐在这里讨论天气
My friend Prew and I sitting here discussing the weather.
你的朋友？
- Your friend huh? - You heard me.
你得好好照顾这个人
Don't you know you gotta take care of this man?
荷姆斯迟早会整倒他
Holmes is bound to get him sooner or later.
他是陆军最棒的士兵
And he's the best stinking' soldier in the whole army.
你们两个都晕头了
You both got rocks in your head.
安杰罗 安杰罗
Angelo Angelo.
我就知道你一定在裘伊酒吧
I figured you'd be here at Choy's.
我办到了 普威特 正如我所说的 我逃出来了
I done it Prew. I escaped just like I said.
跟我所计划的一样
Just like I figured.
跳上了卡车 躲在防水布下面
In the back of a truck under a tarp.
跟我所计划的一样 他们开车把我也载了出来
They rode me right out just like I figured.
可惜离这儿一哩后 后档泥板 就掉了
Only the tailgate opened up Prew about a mile back
所以我跌到路上
and I fell out in the road.
你应该看我弹跳的样子 我应该有骨折才对
You should've seen me bounce. I must've broke something.
普威特 听我说
Prew. Prew listen.
胖子做的 普威特
Fatso done it Prew.
他很喜欢修理我
He likes to whack me in the gut.
一如往常 他问我会不会痛 然后我直接对着他吐口水
He asks me if it hurts and I spit at him like always.
只是昨天 情况很糟
Only yesterday it was bad.
他不断地打我
He hit me he hit me he hit me.
我一定要出来 普威特 我一定要出来
I had to get out Prew. I had to get out.
好家伙
Buddy buddy.
他们会送你回禁闭室 ？
They gonna send you to the stockade Prew?
不 他们不会
No they ain't gonna send me to the stockade.
小心胖子 要小心胖子
Watch out for Fatso.
他想要修理你
He'll try to crack you.
如果他们把你关进单人牢里 千万别大叫
And if they put you in the hole don't yell.
不要出声
Don't make a sound.
否则当他们把你拉出来时 你还是在叫
You'll still be yelling when they come to take you out.
你只管躺在那里
Just lay there.
安安静静地躺在那里 普威特
Just lay there and be quiet Prew.
他死了
He's dead.
我打赌那一定是普威特
I'll betcha that's Prewitt.
贾德森上士
Sergeant Judson?
你找我吗？
You want me?
是的 胖子
Yeah Fatso.
我不喜欢那个外号
I don't like that nickname.
你找我有什么事吗？
You want to see me about something?
我们找个角落好好谈谈
Let's step around the corner where we can talk.
好的
Okay.
- 你在生气什么吗？- 我不喜欢你弹琴的方式
- Are you sore about something? - I don't like the way you play the piano.
- 还记得马吉欧吗？- 义大利佬？
- Remember Maggio? - Oh the wop?
记得 那个泼猴
Yeah a real tough monkey.
- 你杀了他 - 我有吗？
- You killed him. - Did I?
如果我有 也是他咎由自取
Well if I did he asked for it.
军队迟早会惩罚你
The army's gonna get you sooner or later Fatso.
可是在他们动手之前 我想先找你算算帐
But before they do I want a piece of you myself.
我早知道了
I figured that.
看到这把刀了吗？
See this knife?
是你先前威胁马吉欧时所用的
It's the one you pulled on Maggio.
普威特
Prew
出了什么事？
What's...
普威特
Prew
没事了
It's all right.
别担心 别担心 我死不了
Don't worry don't worry. I ain't gonna die.
全数到齐
First platoon all present and accounted for
Second platoon all present and accounted for
全数到齐
First platoon all present and accounted for
Second platoon all present and accounted for
全数到齐
Third platoon all present and accounted for
First platoon all present and accounted for
队伍解散
Company dismissed
普威特还是没有出席
Prewitt's still absent.
已经三天了
Makes three days now.
你还要替他瞒多久？
How long are you gonna carry him present Top?
- 我只是说说 - 那么就别再说了
- I just mention it. - Well don't mention it.
"督察长
"Upon observing these incidents
展开调查
"an investigation was made by the Inspector General's department
这些事件数个月
"over a period of several months.
发现荷姆斯上尉 对普威特士兵残酷的罪行
"It was found that Captain Holmes has been guilty of indefensible cruelty
是无可辩解的
"to the aforesaid Private Prewitt.
其中包括唆使运用 未经许可的方式
"As mentioned this included the instigation of wholly unauthorized tactics
意图强迫他参加军团拳击赛"
"to force the soldier to join the inter-regiment boxing team."
我正在等你回答
I'm waiting for your reply.
我无话可说 长官
I haven't any sir.
荷姆斯 我在军队中 学习到的第一件事
Holmes the first thing I learned in the army
就是军官要好好照顾部属
was that an officer takes care of his men.
但这似乎是你最早忘记的事
It seems to be the first thing that you forgot.
我很遗憾必须让你保留军职
My only regret is that we have to keep you in uniform
直到军事法庭做出判决
until a court-martial is concluded.
若有办法能免除上军事法庭
If there were any way to avoid a court-martial sir.
如果你愿意的话 将军 我倒有另一项选择
There is one alternative General if you are so disposed.
依照陆军规定辞职
A resignation for the good of the service under army regulations.
下午就提出辞呈
Write a letter of resignation. Have it on my desk this afternoon.
据我所知
As far as I'm concerned
你愈快离开陆军 对大家愈有利
the quicker you're out of the army the better for everybody
尤其是对陆军
especially the army.
就这样决定 荷姆斯
That's all Holmes.
我很清楚事情的发展
I know what's been going on in this outfit.
也知道你有多么过份
I know how far some of you have been out of line.
如果你还想继任无委任状士官 就得赶紧努力
If you want to remain noncoms you'd better snap into it.
从现在开始
And another thing from now on
拳击已无法替任何人赢得官阶
no man's gonna earn his stripes by boxing.
- 把那些扔掉 - 是的 长官
- Get rid of those. - Yes sir.
解散
Dismissed.
- 关于葛罗维奇上士 - 是的 长官
- About Sergeant Galovitch. - Yes sir.
将他降级为葛罗维奇大兵
Bust him. Sergeant Galovitch is now Private Galovitch.
派他去管厕所
Put him in charge of the latrine.
你在笑什么？
What are you grinning at?
军团连长做了明智决定
I think the company commander made a wise decision sir.
参谋部 罗斯上尉
Company Captain Ross.
- 请等一下 你的电话 - 谢谢你 长官
- Just a minute. It's for you Sergeant. - Thank you sir.
是的 长官
Yes sir?
是的 包裹已经到了
Yes the parcel has already arrived.
什么？
What?
我必须见你一面 这件事很重要
I've got to see you Milt. It's important.
好的 我想办法去 当然 没有问题
Okay I'll get away somehow. Sure that'd be fine.
我一小时之内赶到
Yeah. I'll be there in about an hour.
好的
Right.
他下礼拜就要被送回去
He's being sent back to the States. He's sailing next week.
他要我跟他一起走 我们怎么办？
He wants me to go with him. What'll we do?
你何时能拿到派令？
When do you think you'll get your commission?
我没有申请
I didn't put it in.
我是填好了但并没有签名
I filled it out but I didn't sign it.
我把它拿出来许多次 但就是无法签名
I took it out of my desk a dozen times but I couldn't sign it.
为什么？
Why?
- 这是我们的计划
But it was the plan.
- 我知道 - 还有好几周时间
- I know I know. - It's been weeks.
你不能光说不做
You can't just say you'll do a thing and then not do it.
凯伦 听我说
Karen listen to me.
你为什么不申请？你为什么不告诉我？
But why didn't you do it? Why didn't you tell me?
我马上回来
Be back in a minute.
对不起 我以为你是某人
I'm sorry. I thought you were somebody else.
我以为是我们军团的普威特
I thought it was a guy from our company Prewitt the kid I was telling you about.
他迷上俱乐部的女孩
The one that got mixed up with one of the girls at the New Congress Club.
他不假外出 可能有大麻烦
He's A.W.O.L. Probably in lots of trouble.
罗勃普威特是个疯狂的坏家伙
Robert E. Lee Prewitt a crazy no good...
凯伦 我不是当军官的料 我是个军人
Karen I'm no officer. I'm an enlisted man.
别的事我都做不来
I can't be anything else.
我一定只会装装样子
If I try to be an officer I'll be putting on an act.
我就是办不到 请不要问我原因
I just can't do it. Please don't ask me why.
我知道原因
I know why.
因为现在唐纳已经离开军队
You don't have to become an officer now Milt
所以你用不着去当军官
now that Dana's out of the army.
你就是不想娶我
You just don't want to marry me.
你己经结了婚 娶了陆军
You're already married to the army.
我是爱你的 凯伦
I love you Karen.
我知道 我知道
I know. I know.
我不希望你回到他身边
I don't want you to go back to Holmes.
我也不想但我是在他身边
I don't want to either but I am.
我已经无能为力
There's nothing else for me to do.
对我们并没有好处 从来不可能有好结果
It's no good with us Milt. It could never have been any good.
这样东躲西藏
Hiding and sneaking.
磨耗了我们的感情
It had to wear out.
再见了 上士
Goodbye Sergeant.
- 谢谢 - 这不是再见而是…
- Thanks. - It ain't goodbye. It's...
总有一天我们会再某处重逢
We'll see each other again somewhere.
我们当然会
Of course we will.
就在某处
Somewhere.
有消息了 已经登在内页
Here it is. Got it on an inside page already.
"谋杀詹姆士贾德森上士凶手 至今仍毫无线索"
"Still no clue in the fatal stabbing of Staff Sergeant James R. Judson."
你听见我说的吗？
Did you hear me?
你想创下新世界纪录吗？
- Trying to set a new world's record? - Yeah.
是的 我就是这么打算
Yeah as a matter of fact I am.
纪念罗勃普威特
To the memory of Robert E. Lee Prewitt
新世界纪录保持人
holder of the new world's record.
- 还好吗？军士长 - 好极了
- Everything all right Top? - Great.
这是在星期天的一顿美味餐
This is a beautiful meal to put in front of a guy on a Sunday morning.
恭喜你了
Congratulations.
- 从山上看下去真美 - 说得也是？
- Sure look pretty over them mountains. - Don't they though?
他们要轰炸车轮草原吗？
Sounds like they're dynamiting down at Wheeler Field.
真是有野心 是吧？星期天早上还不到八点钟
Mighty ambitious huh? Sunday morning before 8:00?
日本战机正在轰炸车轮草原
The Japs are bombing Wheeler Field
我看到红圆圈…
I seen the red circles on the...
到里面去 快一点
Come on get inside Hurry up Go
这是真的 不是演习 日本人正在轰炸珍珠港
This is a real attack not a maneuver. The Japanese are bombing Pearl Harbor.
请留在室内 不要任意外出
Please keep in your homes. Do not go on the streets. This is a real attack.
日本战机正在轰炸 我方的海军及陆军设施
Japanese planes are bombing our naval and army installations.
好了 各位 安静
All right all right you guys quiet down.
安静下来
Quiet Quiet down
士官们 快去拿机关枪和弹药
Noncoms get B.A.R.s and ammunition from the supply room.
- 然后到屋顶上去 韩德生 - 在这 警官
- Get up on the roof. Henderson. - Right here Sarge.
你负责装填子弹 动作快一点
You're in charge of the loading detail. Get moving.
威尔逊多尔 我们走
Wilson Dole let's go.
其他人快去拿步枪
The rest of you men listen to me.
然后回卧铺去 留在那里别动
I want every man to get his rifle go to his bunk and stay there.
我要你们留在那里
And I mean stay there
闭嘴
Shut up
你们到外面会被击中 你们有机会成为英雄
You'll get your ears shot off if you go outside.
你们想逞英雄的话 机会多得是
You wanna be heroes you'll get plenty of chances.
在夜晚来临之前
There'll probably be Japs in your lap before night.
日本人就会坐在你的大腿上
Now get moving. We're wasting time.
嘿 跟上 快点
Hey come on. Hurry up.
等等 去厨房煮一壶咖啡
Wait. Into the kitchen and make a pot of coffee.
- 等一下 煮一桶咖啡 - 好的 警官
- Wait a minute. A barrel of coffee - Right Sarge
我不在乎 没有命令
I don't care. I can't issue any live ammunitions
我不能发给弹药
without a signed order from an officer.
- 可是上尉不在营里 - 很抱歉
- But the captain ain't here you jerk - I'm sorry.
- 没命令没弹药 - 怎么回事？列瓦
- No order no ammo. - What's the matter Leva?
我奉命如此 陆军规定…
I got my orders Army regulations say that I can't give out...
你瞎了吗？把钥匙拿来
What's the matter are you blind? Give me them keys
我奉命如此
I obey my orders Top.
我会看着你得到勋章 冲开
Okay I'll see you get a medal Bust it down boys
我警告过你
I warned ya
别出去 你会没命的
Don't go out there Warden You'll get killed
快点穿衣服 你会着凉的
Put your pants on. You'll catch cold
快帮他们处理弹药 把那个东西放在那边
Give him a hand with this ammo. Put that stuff over there.
小心开火 瞄准飞机前方
Watch your fire boys and lead those planes
他正在吹"骑兵突袭乐"
Friday's gone crazy He's blowing the cavalry charge
他们来了 各位
Here they come boys
你打中他了 彼得 你打中他了
You got him Pete You got him
我打中他了？
I got him?
入侵的危机仍然存在
The danger of an invasion continues to exist.
雪菲得部队在数小时内移防 并已就滩头位置
Infantry units from Schofield Barracks moved out within a few hours
我打中他了
and have manned beach positions.
这不是演习 这是真正打仗
This is no maneuver. This is the real McCoy.
小心榴霰弹 快找掩护
Look out for falling shrapnel. Keep under cover.
将实施灯火管制及宵禁
Blackout and curfew restrictions will be rigidly enforced.
请留在家中并不要使用电话
Stay in your homes. Don't use the telephone.
我们传播所有资讯…
Rest assured that immediate relay to you...
我们到皇家医院捐血了
Prew We've been to Queen's Hospital giving blood.
简直混乱极了
The town's a madhouse.
库希欧有房子遭到轰炸
There's a big house bombed out on Kuhio Street.
一间杂货店被夷为平地
And the drugstore down on McCully and King is smashed flat.
- 有对夫妇因而丧生 - 各位请注意
- Man and his wife were killed. - Your attention please.
请各位注意 注意听好并保持镇静
Listen to this carefully and keep calm.
入侵的危机仍然存在
The danger of an invasion continues to exist
进行轰炸的飞机 已确认属日方所有
and the planes have been identified as Japanese.
他们以为在向谁挑衅？
Who do they think they're fighting?
他们正在对抗 世界上最精良的陆军
They're picking trouble with the best army in the world.
你要上哪儿去？
Where are you going?
我必须回去 我必须回部队去
I gotta get back. I gotta get back to the company.
- 部队？为什么？- 为什么？
- The company? But why? - Why?
不可以 你还没有复原
But you can't. You're not well yet.
你会被关到禁闭室
Besides you're A.W.O.L. They'll throw you in the stockade.
他们会把他们丢到栅栏外
They'll be throwing them out of the stockade.
- 他们需要所有能用的人手 - 但你的伤口会裂开
- They need every guy they can get. - But your side'll open up.
他们会知道是你杀了那个士官
They'll find out it was you who killed that soldier.
只要我向部队报到 他们就会照顾我的
Once I report in to the company they'll take care of me.
我会没事的 我会安全回来
I'll be all right once I get back.
你绝对到不了的 到处都有人在巡逻
But you'll never make it There's patrols all over
我到得了 我知道捷径
I'll make it. I know a shortcut.
留到天亮再说吧
Prew stay till morning.
或许你明天就会改变心意
Maybe if you stay till morning you'll change your mind.
普威特 不要走
Oh Prew don't go
我会照你的话去做
I'll do anything you want.
我们可以一起回美国 甚至我们可以结婚
We can go back to the States together. We can even get married.
若你走了 我再也见不到你
If you go now I'll never see you again I know it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你为什么想回去？
What do you want to go back to the army for?
陆军根本视你如粪土…
What did the army ever do for you besides treat you like dirt
经常殴打你 还害你朋友丧命
and give you one awful going-over and get your friend killed?
你为什么想回去？
What do you want to go back to the army for?
我为什么想回去？因为我是军人
What do I want to go back to the army for? I'm a soldier.
军人？一个常备兵？
A soldier? A soldier?
一个陆军 一个准备当兵三十年的人
A regular From the regular army A 30-year man
外面正在实施灯火管制 所以我得把灯关掉
I gotta turn off the lights 'cause of the blackout outside.
山上有伞兵降落
They say they've seen parachutists land up in the hills.
我并不担心他们 我担心的是破坏分子
I ain't worried about them. Saboteurs is what worries me.
是的 我打赌他们一定遍布全岛
Yeah. I bet they're operating all over these islands.
不要动
Halt
我顺利的星期一
My hitch was up Monday
不是个失败的士兵
Not a dog soldier no more
我不再是个士兵
Soldier no more
他们给了我所有的钱
They give me all that money
多到我口袋很沉重
So much my pockets is sore
你认识这个人吗？上士
Do you know this man Sergeant?
是的 长官
Yes sir.
他没有任何身分证明
He didn't have any regular identification.
他们找到有他名字的卡片
They found a card on him with his name.
好像是俱乐部的会员证
Seems to be a membership in a club.
- 新国会俱乐部 - 是的 长官
- The New Congress Club. - Yes sir.
你最好处理一下
You'd better take care of these Sergeant.
- 他是你的朋友吗？- 是的长官
- Was this man a friend of yours? - Yes sir.
他一定是想回到海滩上的部队
He must've been trying to reach our company position up the beach here.
那么为什么他不停止？
Then why didn't he halt?
他是死脑筋但却是个好军人
He was always a hardhead sir but he was a good soldier.
他是我认识的所有人中 最爱陆军的
He loved the army more than any soldier I ever knew.
我明白了 很遗憾 上士
I see. I'm sorry Sergeant.
你就是不能从善如流
You just couldn't play it smart could you?
不过是要你打拳罢了 可是你这个死脑筋就是不肯
All you had to do was box. But no not you you hardhead.
好笑的是 今年没有拳击冠军
Funny thing is there ain't gonna be any boxing championships this year.
没有看过死人吗？
What's the matter with you? Ain't you ever seen a dead man?
把尸体抬出去
Let's get this body outta here We ain't got all night
真美 是吧？
It's very beautiful isn't it?
我想这是我此生见过 最美的一个地方
I think it's the most beautiful place I ever saw in my life.
我几乎能看见我工作的地方
I can almost see where I worked from here.
听说有个传说
There's a legend.
如果花环漂向海岸 表示你还会再回来
If they float in toward shore you'll come back someday.
如果是向外漂 你就不会回来
If they float out to sea you won't.
我不会再回来了
I won't come back.
我的未婚夫在十二月七日被杀
You see my fiance was killed on December 7th.
真是遗─感
Oh I'm sorry.
他原是个轰炸机飞行员
He was a bomber pilot.
当他把飞机滑到停机坪边缘…
He tried to taxi his plane to the edge of the apron
日军直接击中他
and the Japs made a direct hit on it.
或许你曾在报上看过消息
Maybe you read about it in the papers.
他获授银星勋章
He was awarded the silver star.
军方将勋章送给他母亲
They sent it to his mother.
她写信给我 要我保留它
She wrote me she wanted me to have it.
她真好
That's very fine of her.
南方人都很好
They're very fine people. Southern people.
他以某位将军的名字为名
He was named after a general.
罗勃 普威特
Robert E. Lee Prewitt.
谁？
Who?
罗勃普威特
Robert E. Lee Prewitt.
真是个愚蠢的老名字吧？
Isn't that a silly old name?